<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="rss.css" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>Damaj301Damaj's Personal RSS feed</title>
  <link>https://Damaj301damaj-lol.github.io/RSS-feed/</link>
  <description>Personal feed of Damaj301damaj, contains variety of topics, depends on what i feel like to, proudly written in vim/busybox vi on multiple hosts</description>
  <item>
    <title>First post</title>
    <link>https://Damaj301damaj-lol.github.io/RSS-feed/html/00000.html</link>
    <guid>0000000000</guid>
    <pubDate>2022-06-9</pubDate>
    <description>
	    <p>Hello!, well this is the first post, still experimenting, i hope you will enjoy some content soon :-D.</p>
   </description>
  </item>
  <item>
	<title>Why is the Wii still loved by people?</title>
	<link>https://Damaj301damaj-lol.github.io/RSS-feed/html/00001.html</link>
        <guid>0000000001</guid>
	<pubDate>2022-06-11</pubDate>
	<description>
		<p>First, a bit of history.</p>
		<p>The Wii is a console made by Nintendo, it was a big success, it sold over 100 million copies and people loved it, especially because of its gimmicks and games, games like Mario Kart Wii really helped pushing sales, and now, the wii can be found for very cheap and in quantities</p>
		<p>Now, back to the title, we are now in 2022, and the wii is still loved, i know you might be asking how?</p>
		<p>Well we are gonna go over some reasons on why the wii is still loved until today</p>
		<p>1) The Wii has great games that are not *that* easy to emulate. We have Dolphin, and its near perfect, and i appreciate the effort, but due to how much the wii has gimmicks, you cannot deny that having a wii/wii u is the best way to play Wii Games, with a Wiimote, on your feets, excited</p>
		<p>2) The Wii is a great Homebrew box, The fan community has done a lot to this underpowered console, compared to the same generation's original Xbox and PS2, due to how easy it is to homebrew, before, you needed The Legend of Zelda, Twillight princess and an sd card, now you can do it without Any Game, and even no sd card, and the Wii can emulate a lot of consoles, and the Wii got great Homebrew ports!</p>
		<p>3) The Wii is cheap and easy to find, like literally, go to your favorite local shopping site and find a used Wii, it will be very cheap, and if not, i am sorry but the Wii wasn't that of a sucess in your country.</p>
		<p>4) The Wii feels no different compared to how it was in 2010... somewhat, if you install services like RiiConnect24 and Wiimmfi, it really returns the Wii's online features that nintendo had taken away from us. </p>
		<p>And that's all i have to say, i hope you liked this reading and see you again in a next post!</p>
	</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
